<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- How many hosts is configured to be blocked (the blacklist). Parameter: number of hosts. -->
    <!-- Shown on the Home screen instead of the Hosts count whenever hosts are being processed. -->
    <!-- Shown on the Home screen instead of the Hosts count whenever hosts are being downloaded. -->
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_now_title">다운로드 목록</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_now">지금 다운로드 목록</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_toast">Download of lists started</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_now_description">아래의 버튼을 사용하여 캐시를 제거하고 목록을 다시 다운로드하십시오. 필터링 문제가 발생하면 도움이 될 수 있습니다.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_frequency_title">수시로 목록 다운로드</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_frequency_description">Select one of the options to configure how often the app should download your lists.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_frequency_1">하루에 한 번</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_frequency_2">주 2 회</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_frequency_3">일주일에 한 번</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_frequency_4">한 달에 한 번</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_frequency_5">Never</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_wifi_only_title">Wi-Fi 에서 만 다운로드</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_wifi_only_description">기기가 Wi-Fi에 연결된 경우에만 앱이 목록을 다운로드하도록하려면이 스위치를 활성화합니다. 그렇지 않으면 휴대 기기가 모바일 네트워크에 연결되어 있고 데이터 요금제를 사용하는 경우 앱에서 목록을 다운로드 할 수도 있습니다.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_watchdog_title">Watchdog</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_watchdog_description">Activate this switch if you wish the app to activate the VPN only if there is Internet connectivity, and restart the tunnel in case there are connectivity problems. This may help for some devices.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_powersave_title">Aggressive wakeup</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_powersave_description">Activate this switch if you experience problems caused by your device\'s powersave feature. When the app detects tunnel connectivity problems, it will attempt to raise its priority to bring it out of the powersaving mode.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_reports_title">Reports</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_reports_description">Activate this switch to allow the app to send reports helping us fix problems and bugs. This will happen only once per day, or when the app crashes. Disabling this may make it hard for us to solve any problems you may be experiencing. You may need to restart the app for this setting to take effect.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_wildcard_title">[BETA] Advanced adblocking rules</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_wildcard_description">Activate this switch if you wish to use wildcards in your filtering rules. For example, adding a rule for *.google.com would block all domains from Google. This may have a negative impact on battery life. Please note that this is an experimental feature, and may not work properly.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_cname_title">[BETA] CName-Blocking</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_cname_description">Activate this switch if you want to block all CNames for the domains on your block lists. A CName is an alias for a domain, which is used by some advertiser to hide this domain behind a often changing or less obvious domain. This tactic can be circumvented by blocking all CNames that would resolve to the blocked domain. Please note that this is an experimental feature, and may not work properly.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_fallback_title">DNS fallback</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_fallback_description">Activate this switch if you are losing Internet access in some situations, like your WiFi. This will make the app temporarily switch to Cloudflare or Google DNS to sustain your connectivity. You may need to re-select your servers in the DNS section for this setting to take effect.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_title">[BETA] Smart List</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_reset_btn">초기화</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_clean_btn">Clean</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_clean_none">Nothing to clean</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_clean_inactive">Smart List inactive</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_clean_done">Smart List got cleaned of old rules</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_reset_done">Smart List got reset</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_description">Activate this switch to enable Smart List feature, which dramatically decreases the number of rules in your filters, potentially improving battery life and lowering RAM usage. When enabled, Blokada will look at your request log, and dynamically generate a list that only contains rules that actually blocked at least one request. The Smart List is updated daily at night. Please note that you may experience a higher number of unwanted requests being allowed during the learning period (a few days). Please note that this is an experimental feature, and may not work properly.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_disable_wildcard">Disable Advanced adblocking rules first.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_disable_smartlist">Disable Smart List first.</string>
</resources>
