<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- How many hosts is configured to be blocked (the blacklist). Parameter: number of hosts. -->
    <!-- Shown on the Home screen instead of the Hosts count whenever hosts are being processed. -->
    <!-- Shown on the Home screen instead of the Hosts count whenever hosts are being downloaded. -->
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_now_title">Last ned lister</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_now">Last ned lister nå</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_toast">Nedlasting av lister startet</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_now_description">Bruk knappen nedenfor for å fjerne cache og last ned lister på nytt. Dette kan hjelpe hvis du opplever problemer med filtreringene dine.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_frequency_title">Nedlastingshyppighet for lister</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_frequency_description">Select one of the options to configure how often the app should download your lists.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_frequency_1">En gang om dagen</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_frequency_2">To ganger i uken</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_frequency_3">En gang i uken</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_frequency_4">En gang i måneden</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_refetch_frequency_5">Aldri</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_wifi_only_title">Last ned kun med Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_wifi_only_description">Aktiver denne bryteren hvis du vil at appen bare skal laste ned lister når enheten er koblet til WiFi. Ellers kan appen også laste ned lister når enheten din er koblet til et mobilnettverk, og bruke dataplanen din.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_watchdog_title">Vakthund</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_watchdog_description">Activate this switch if you wish the app to activate the VPN only if there is Internet connectivity, and restart the tunnel in case there are connectivity problems. This may help for some devices.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_powersave_title">Aggressiv oppvåkning</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_powersave_description">Activate this switch if you experience problems caused by your device\'s powersave feature. When the app detects tunnel connectivity problems, it will attempt to raise its priority to bring it out of the powersaving mode.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_reports_title">Rapporter</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_reports_description">Aktiver denne bryteren for å la appen sende rapporter som hjelper oss med å løse problemer og feil. Dette vil skje bare en gang per dag, eller når appen krasjer. Deaktivering av dette kan gjøre det vanskelig for oss å løse eventuelle problemer du måtte oppleve. Du må kanskje starte appen på nytt for at denne innstillingen skal tre i kraft.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_wildcard_title">[BETA] Oppføringer med jokertegn</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_wildcard_description">Activate this switch if you wish to use wildcards in your filtering rules. For example, adding a rule for *.google.com would block all domains from Google. This may have a negative impact on battery life. Please note that this is an experimental feature, and may not work properly.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_cname_title">[BETA] CName-Blocking</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_cname_description">Activate this switch if you want to block all CNames for the domains on your block lists. A CName is an alias for a domain, which is used by some advertiser to hide this domain behind a often changing or less obvious domain. This tactic can be circumvented by blocking all CNames that would resolve to the blocked domain. Please note that this is an experimental feature, and may not work properly.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_fallback_title">DNS-tilbakefall</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_fallback_description">Activate this switch if you are losing Internet access in some situations, like your WiFi. This will make the app temporarily switch to Cloudflare or Google DNS to sustain your connectivity. You may need to re-select your servers in the DNS section for this setting to take effect.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_title">[BETA] Smartliste</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_reset_btn">Nullstill</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_clean_btn">Tøm</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_clean_none">Nothing to clean</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_clean_inactive">Smart List inactive</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_clean_done">Smart List got cleaned of old rules</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_reset_done">Smart List got reset</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_smartlist_description">Activate this switch to enable Smart List feature, which dramatically decreases the number of rules in your filters, potentially improving battery life and lowering RAM usage. When enabled, Blokada will look at your request log, and dynamically generate a list that only contains rules that actually blocked at least one request. The Smart List is updated daily at night. Please note that you may experience a higher number of unwanted requests being allowed during the learning period (a few days). Please note that this is an experimental feature, and may not work properly.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_disable_wildcard">Disable Advanced adblocking rules first.</string>
    <string name="tunnel_config_disable_smartlist">Disable Smart List first.</string>
</resources>
